嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
抱歉迟到了  没错过什么吧
Sorry I'm late. Did I miss anything?
乔伊在嘴里放了15块奥立奥饼干
Joey stuffing fifteen Oreos in his mouth.
15片
Fifteen?
刷新个人纪录哦
Your personal best! Ha, ha.
你到哪儿去了
So Where were you?
赴了个约会
On a date.
我去逛城郊的博物馆  在火车上认识了一个女孩
I met this girl on a train going to a museum upstate.
哪间博物馆  你是怎么认识她的
Oh, Which museum? Oh, yeah! How'd you meet her?
不用理我  回答他的问题
No. Answer his.
好吧  火车后厢就我们两个人
Okay, it was just me and her at the back of the train,
我的座位靠门  她要换车的话
and I sat near the door so she'd have to pass by me
就得从我边上过  她拿我没办法
...if she wanted to switch cars. She was totally at my mercy.
你迟到是因为和她神侃吗
Were you so late because you were burring this woman?
不是  我赶紧回来了  因为她住在Poughkeepsie（纽约州东南部）
No, I'm getting back down 'cause she lives in Poughkeepsie.
她看上去真的很不错  住在2个半小时的路程之外
She seems really great, but she lives two and a half hours away.
都住在Poughkeepsie了  怎么还会很棒
How can she be great if she's from Poughkeepsie? Ha-ha-ha.
到Albany（纽约州首府）就没笑话可讲了
That joke would have killed in Albany.
好了  我吃下去了
Done! I did it!
现在谁才傻啊
Heh, Who's stupid now?
老友记  第四季  第10集  乱点鸳鸯谱
Friends S04E10  The one with the girl from Poughkeepsie
（主演：詹妮弗·安妮斯顿）
（主演：柯特妮·考克斯）
（主演：丽莎·库卓）
（主演：马特·勒布朗）
（主演：马修·派瑞）
（主演：大卫·修蒙）
嘿  看这个  今晚他们要点亮这棵大圣诞树
Hey, look at this! They're lighting the big Christmas tree tonight.
那是两周前的报纸
Um, that paper is two weeks old.
是谁老是把旧报纸  丢在垃圾桶里的
All right, Who keeps leaving old newspapers in the trash?
我本来想带凯西去看  没想到居然错过了
I really wanted to take Kathy to this. I can't believe I missed it.
嘿  你至少还有人可以和你一起“错过”机会
Hey, y'know, at least you have somebody to miss that stuff with!
我已经孤独整整一年了
I hate being alone this time of year.
接着我又要一个人过情人节
Next thing it'll be Valentine's Day...
我的生日  然后又是"嗙"
...then my birthday, then bang!
在你反应过来之前  又是圣诞节了
before you know it, they're lighting that damn tree again.
噢  我想有人陪
Ohh, I want somebody!
我要个真正的"男人"
You know, I want a man!
我是说  哪怕不是正式的交往  而只是"逢场作戏"一次也好
I mean, it doesn't even have to be a big relationship. y'know, just like a fling would be great.
真的  我还以为女孩子从来不想搞"一夜情"的呢
Really?! I didn’t think girls ever just wanted a fling.
我告诉你  我很早以前就来过"一夜情"了
Let me tell you, it's been a long time since I've been flung.
噢  那我知道圣诞节要送你什么了
Well, I know what I'm giving you for Christmas.
我有几个同事挺不错的  要不要帮你介绍一下
There are nice guys in my office. Want me to set you up?
好啊
Yeah.
好啊  等等  我已经单身好久了  你以前为什么不提
Yeah! Wait a minute, it's been a long time that I've been single. How come you never offered this before?
我现在有女朋友了  很快乐
Well, I have a girlfriend, I'm-I'm happy.
所以  我不再需要把快乐建筑在他人的痛苦之上了
So, I no longer feel the need to go out of my way to stop others from being happy.
好
Okay.
我不要会计师
No accountants.
也不要律师  我不喜欢工作无聊的男人
And no one from "legal." I don't like boring jobs.
噢  罗斯工作不无聊吗  他是驯兽师么
Oh and Ross was like what? A lion tamer?
怎么回事  莫妮
What's wrong, Mon?
餐馆的所有人都恨我
Ohh, everybody at the restaurant still hates me.
本来我想我的人缘好起来了
I thought I was making headway.
大家都冲着我微笑  下班后
Everyone was smiling at me all day, and then I get off work
才发现他们在我帽子上写了这个
and find out that they wrote this on my chef's hat.
（婊子  快辞职）
也许他们想写的是 "婊子  快住嘴"
Hey, maybe they meant to write, "Quiet, Bitch."
嘿  亲爱的  怎么了
Hey, honey! What's the matter?
干嘛  火气这么大
Fine! Just trying to be nice.
从幼儿园后  我就没被这么捉弄过了
I haven't been picked on this much since kindergarten.
当时他们找了个国中生 来监视我
And they brought in someone from junior high to do the see-saw with me.
他们想尽办法赶我走
I mean they're trying to do everything they can to make me quit,
换做是别的工作  我早就不干了
and if there were any other job, I would.
但是这是我一生都想从事的职业
This is something I've been waiting for my whole life.
哦  等等  你是老大
Well, wait a minute, you're the boss.
为什么不吼他们  或干脆炒了他们
Why don't you just yell at them? Or, fire them?
我也很想这样  可是我做不到  我最不会处理这种冲突
I would love to, but I can't. you know that I'm not good at confrontation.
嘿  你知道你该怎么办么
Hey, You know what you can do?
我记得我曾读过一个导演的书  好像是奥森威尔斯 ("公民凯恩"的导演)
I remember read about this director, I think it was Orson Wells,
他会在电影开拍前  雇一个人
who at the beginning of the movie would hire somebody,
然后当着大伙的面  解雇他
just so he could fire them in front of everybody.
这样那些人就会明白  谁才是头儿
Then they would all know who was boss.
嘿  莫妮卡  反正我没事  你干脆开除我算了
Hey, Mon! I'm not doing anything, why don't you fire me?
好主意  你知道怎么当服务生吗
I's a good idea! do you know waiter?
反正你要开除我  管那么多干嘛
Good enough to get fired.
好  我决定用你了
All right. You're hired!
嘿
Hey!
难怪我上个礼拜被开除  奥森威尔斯是不是也掌管汉堡包的生意
Hey! That must be why I got fired last week! Does this Orson Wells guy direct Burger King commercials?
有
Yes.
我说的是  德  你现在有没有人约会
I say, Drew? Are you seeing anybody right now?
哦  我不是在帮我自己问
Og-ee-op, I'm not asking for me.
我  我  我不是同性恋  我不是想约你
I’m… I mean… No, I'm-I'm not gay, I'm not asking you out.
我不是同志
I'm not gay. Okey!
我从不认为你是同性恋
I didn't think you were gay.
不过现在拿不准了
I do now.
我朋友瑞秋  希望我帮她介绍个男人
See my friend-my friend, Rachel, she wants to be set up.
我才刚刚跟前女友分手
Ahh,I just got out of a big relationship.
我现在不想跟谁交往
I'm not looking for any thing serious.
你知道么  哪怕是“逢场作戏”都行  没问题的
Oh, y'know what, that might be okay even if it was just kind of a fling, that might be all right with Rachel.
喔  喔  喔  是不是你曾带到圣诞晚会上的那个 "火辣瑞秋"吗
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Is this "Hot Rachel" that you took to the Christmas Party? Rachel?
没错  那就是她的全名
Oh, By the way, that is her full name.
我有空   帮我介绍一下吧
Wow! I'm free for her.
等等  我又没说我没空
Oh, wait a second! I didn't say I wasn't free.
嘿  钱德  我们在明天"游骑兵"队的比赛上谈谈这个事呢
Hey, Chandler, I'll talk so at the Ranger game tomorrow?
打住  我刚得到一盒古巴雪茄
Hold on. y'know I just got a box of Cubans.
也许我可以拿到你办公室去  5点钟怎么样
maybe I bring them by your office around uh, five?
这个么  我平常不会待到这么晚  不过可以破个例
that's uh, a little later than I uh, generally care to stay, but sure!
也许比赛前
Maybe, before the game
我们可以去享受两瓶8年陈酿的巴素海顿波本
we can enjoy some eight year old some small batch Basel Hadens.
天晓得那是什么东东  但好吧
Well, I don't really know what that is, but let's!
嘿  你们几个  我为所有人写了个节日歌  你们想听么
Hey! You guys, I'm writing a holiday song for everyone. Do you want to hear it?
好啊  好
Yeah! Yes!
摩妮卡  光明节快乐
Happy Hanukkah, Monica
乔伊  愿你圣诞节瑞雪纷飞
May your Christmas be snowy, Joey
钱德  罗斯  新年快乐
Happy New Year, Chandler and Ross
瑞秋  快来转陀螺
Spin the dreidel, Rachel
菲比  真好听  太棒了
Pheebs, that's great! Oh, yay!
但是瑞秋跟陀螺不押韵
But you know, uh, Rachel doesn't rhyme with dreidel.
我知道  但是你的垃圾名字实在很难找到压韵的词
I know, but it's so hard. Nothing rhymes with your stupid name!
不会呀  跟瑞秋押韵的字多得很
What are you talking about? Lots of things rhyme with Rachel:
如贝果  信件  监狱  保释金  第四台…
Bagel, mail, jail, bail, cable.
五月柱…
Maypole.
那些都不错  谢了
All good. Thanks.
你有没有比较容易押韵的外号什么的
Do you maybe have a nickname that's easier to rhyme?
你爸以前  不是常叫你小南瓜吗
Didn't your dad call you "Pumpkin"?
对  没错
Oh, yeah.
Pumpkin  好吧  但他有没有叫过你布道夫
Pumpkin? Yeah. But did he ever call you "Budolph"?
大家好  嘿
Hello, children. Hey.
我帮你找了50个候选男人
Have I got the 50 guys for you!
真的么  我不过把你的照片亮给他们看
Really? Oh yeah, I just showed this a picture of you and
他们就全都蜂拥而上
guys were throwing themselves at me!
他们又是请我喝酒  又是送我东西
They're buying me drinks! They're giving me stuff!
今晚看球赛  当然  座位在哪儿
Knicks tonight? Sure! Where are the seats?
随你挑  我有20张票
Wherever! I've got 20.
那么  他们中有没有适合我的
So, will I like any of these guys?
你知道的  我想再多…
You know, I'm going to, uh...
观察阵子  钱德
...play the field a little bit more. Chandler...
他们甚至把401-k（养老基金）受益人都填成我啦
Guys are signing over their 401 Ks to me.
你的同事都是机器人(不要养老金)啊
You work with robots?
你说的对
Yes.
其中有个叫派崔克的小伙  我想你应该会喜欢他
Yes. Okay, there's this one guy, Patrick, I think you're gonna like him,
他人好  风趣  还是个游泳健将
He's really nice, funny and a swimmer.
我爱死游泳健将的身材了
I like swimmers' bodies.
而且他老爸还发明了  信用卡背面的识别磁条
Yes, and his father invented that magnetic strip on the back of credit cards.
我也爱死信用卡了
Op, I like credit cards!
你看  这事我办得不错吧
See, I'm not bad at this fixing up thing, huh?
他是做什么工作的  他在精炼食品部门工作
Well, so what does he do? Oh, he works in the Fine Foods division.
你公司还做精炼食品  这可是家大公司  如果你  我
You have a fine foods division? It's a big company,I don't—if you—I…
等等  又做精炼食品又做机器人
Now, wait a second. You make food and robots?
不是啦  机器人是帮忙工作的
No, the robots just work for them.
好了  我得上班去了
All right, I'm going to work.
有人有意见吗
Does anybody have a problem with that?
是的  小姐  我有意见
Yeah, lady. I do!
我就是有意见
I got a problem with that!
你有意见  就别怪我不客气了
You want a problem? I'll give you a problem!
你想怎样  开除我
Oh, what are you gonna do? You're gonna fire me?
你个蠢驴  我解雇你了
You bet your ass I'll fire you!
回头见  谢谢
See you later. Thank you.
噢  喔  我得走了  今晚有约会
Oh, wow! I should get going. I-I got a date tonight.
是么  跟谁
Oh yeah! With who?
还记得那个住在  波放浦夕的女孩吗  记得
You know that girl I told you about who lives up in Poughkeepsie? Yeah.
不是她
Not her.
我又认识了一个女孩
Yeah, this is someone else,
现在左右为难
and I-I can’t decide between the two of them.
波敔浦夕那个女孩  虽然得坐2小时火车才能看到她  但漂亮
The one from Poughkeepsie, even though she's a two hour train ride away, is really pretty...
聪明又有趣
...really smart and a lot of fun.
但另一个女孩  就住在上城区
But this other girl, well，she lives right uptown.
她也很漂亮
Y'know she's, well she's-she's just as pretty,
可能也聪明
I guess she's smart.
但是一点也不风趣
She's not fun.
一点也不风趣  你为什么还要跟她约会
she's no fun, why date her at all?
我想再给她一个机会  对吧  她住的这么近
Well, I-I want to give her a chance. y'know? She lives so close.
而且上次约会的最后  另一次  她曾说了些...
And, at the end of the date, the other time, she-she said something that...
如果是在开玩笑的话  那她就佷风趣
if she was kidding, was very funny.
否则她不仅无聊  而且愚蠢  还有种族歧视
On the other hand, if she wasn't kidding, she's not fun. She's stupid and kind of a racist.
嘿  嘿  伙计
Hey. Hey. Hey, man!
第一天在餐厅工作  情况如何
Hey! Ooh, How was your first day working at the restaurant?
可恶
Damn!
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
你的制服怎么了
What happened to your fancy chef's jacket?
被他们烤了
They baked it.
我再也受不了了
I can't take this anymore.
今晚要开个会  然后解雇你  没问题
I'm gonna call a meeting tonight, I'm gonna fire you tonight.You got it. Oh, oh!
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
你衣服上还有火星
It's still a tiny bit on fire there.
谢谢  你应该已经拍灭了吧
Thanks. I think you got it!
钱德  你对男人的品味一流
Chandler, you have the best taste in men.
有其父必有其子
Well, Like father, like son.
派崔克和我昨晚玩得好开心
Patrick and I had such a great time last night!
说不定能发展出一段  认真的感情
I mean I think this could maybe turn into something serious.
是么  好像不是想要跟谁交往的呀  你只想“放荡”一下
Really?! I-I thought you weren't looking for something serious? I thought you were looking for some kind of a fling.
噢  好像是这样
Well, you know, possibly.
你没告诉他吧
You didn't tell him that, though, right?
没有  我已经说了
Ummmmmmmm, no.
你告诉他我只是想搞"一夜情"
You told this guy that I was looking for a fling?
你怎么能告诉他
You don't tell the guy that!
为什么不行  如果我知道那个火辣的女孩想要  我会兴奋得发抖…
Why not?I'd be thrilled if I heard that some hot girl was just looking to get
噢  我明白了
I see.
你告诉他我想“一夜情”
Oh, between you telling him that I wanted to have a fling
而我想跟他长期交往
and me putting out on the first date
他一定会误会的
oh, he's so gonna get the wrong idea.
乔伊  把芝士递过来么
Hey, Joey, could you pass the cheese?
好的  我想你还是别叫我乔伊
Yeah. Listen uh, I'd prefer you didn't call me Joey.
因为这没人认识我  所以我想帮自己取了个超炫的外号
Since I don't know anyone here, I thought it'd be cool to try out a cool work nickname.
嘿  龙哥
Hey, Dragon!
这是你周一和周二2天赚的小费
Here's your tips from Monday and Tuesday.
天啊  有三百块耶
There's like-there's like 300 bucks in this one!
过节时客人总是特别大方
Yeah, People get generous around the holidays.
穿紧身裤的效果更是很棒
And it never hurts to wear tight trousers.
请服务生集合一下  交代一下今晚的特价菜
Okay. Could the waiters gather around to hear tonight's specials?
首先是用芒果佐味的智利黑鲈
Okay, first there's Chilean sea bass with a mango relish on a bag
你们为什么没人用笔记一下
Why is nobody writing these down?
因为我们能记住
We can remember them.
因为你们这样就能象以前一样随口捏造假的特价菜  然后让我来弄
Because you'll make up fake specials and make me cook them like you did the other night?
哦  没错  也有这个原因
Well, Sure, that too.
好吧  先把特价菜放到一边  是这样的…
Okay, Forget the specials for a minute. Umm, all right here's the thing...
过去两周里  我试着想
For the last two weeks I have, uh...
努力营造一个愉快的工作环境
...tried hard to create a positive atmosphere.
听不到
Can't hear you!
愉快的工作环境
positive atmosphere!
但是现在我对此不抱希望了
But I've had it up to here.
从现在开始  要么按我说得去做
From now on, it is going to be my way
要么就滚蛋
...or the highway. All right?
有人有意见吗
Does anybody have a problem with that?
嘿  新来的
Hey, new guy.
我说有人有意见吗
I said, does anybody have a problem with that?
没有
No, ma'am.
嘿  他有名字  他叫龙哥
Hey! He has a name. It's Dragon.
想知道你的名字吗  看看你的帽子
You want to know your name? Check your hat.
我们写在上面了  是吧
We did the hat, right?
刚刚那是怎么回事  真的很抱歉
What the hell just happened? I am so-so-so sorry.
我真的很想配合你
I was going to do it.Really!
但我一手拿着327块
But I was standing there with $327 in one hand...
另一手拿着238块 我在想...
...and $238 in the other. And I was thinking...
我很久没拿到…
"Wow! It's been a long time since I had…
327块加238块  这么多钱了
...327 plus $238!
乔伊  我们说好的  我用你就是为了开除你
Joey, We had a deal! That-that's why you're here. I've got to fire you!
但是我要付房租的
And I got to pay rent!
这样吧  你别开除我
how-how about this? You don't fire me,
我留在这里争取他们的信任
instead I stay here, I gain their trust.
我说你的好话  他们就听得进去了
and they'll start listening to all the nice things I've been saying about you.
什么好话
What nice things?
还没有  他们恨死你了 我想跟他们打成一片
Well Nothing yet. they really hate you and I want to fit in.
钱德  摩妮卡  光明节快乐  圣诞
Happy Hanukkah, Chandler and Monica, Merry, merry...
菲比  你知道吗
Oh, y'know, y'know what Pheebs?
我不是犹太人  所以...
I'm not Jewish so...
罗斯也没有用绒毛装饰他的圣诞树
So! Ross doesn't really decorate his tree with floss,
他有没有跟你抱怨过  天啊
but you don't hear him complaining do you? God!
做恶梦啦
Bad dream?
我根本没睡着
I wasn't sleeping.
是吗  那菲比刚刚在唱什么歌
Oh yeah, then uh, what was Phoebe's song about?
关于小猫什么的
The one with the cat.
我得走了  又有约会
I got to go. I've got another date.
那么  你选谁了
So, did you pick one yet?
没有  现在反而城里的那个女孩开始讲笑话
No, it turns out the one from uptown was making a joke.
但是我根本不懂她的笑话  而且没那么好笑
But it was a different joke than I thought—it wasn't that funny.
我还是两头跑  左右为难
So I'm still torn.
你看  你根本不喜欢城里的那个女孩
Well look, you don't really like the one from uptown
为了跟波敔浦夕妞约会  累得疲惫不堪
and you're too exhausted from dating the one up in Poughkeepsie,
所以跟他们两个都分手  怎么样
so I say you just end them both. Okay?
坐火车去波敔浦夕跟她分手
You take a train up to Poughkeepsie and break up with her,
然后回来的路上跟城里的那个姑娘也分手
and on your way back you break up with uptown.
到家时一切都解决了  搞定
And then by the time you get home tonight, you're done!
对  你说得对  谢谢
Y'know, You're right. Thank you.
我在布拉格也碰到过这种问题
Umm, well I had a similar problem when I lived in Prague.
布拉格  还有很多事你不知道呢
Prague? So much you don't know.
钱德
Chandler?
派崔克刚刚跟我分手了
Patrick just, uh, ended things with me.
你有没有告诉他  我想认真谈段感情
Did you or did you not tell him that I was looking for a serious relationship?
我说了  当然说了
I did! I absolutely did!
你个白痴
You idiot!
我知道你说得对  但是  为什么
I'm sure you're right. But why?
你不该告诉他我要谈段认真的感情  你不该告诉他的
You don't tell a guy that you're looking for a serious relationship! You don't tell the guy that!
你看  把他吓跑了
Now you scared him away!
噢  伙计  我非常遗憾  我非常非常遗憾
Oh, man. I'm sorry, I'm so-so sorry.
应该禁止你跟别人说话
Y'know, You should never be allowed to talk to people!
我知道  没错
I know, I know!
噢  我又回到起点了
Oh! See just I'm now right back where I started!
超难过
Aww, this sucks!
孤孤单单的真难过
Being alone sucks!
呃  你知道  你迟早会遇见意中人
Well, y'know, you're-you're gonna meet somebody!
你是个好对象
You're a great catch!
你知道么  我跟同事形容你时  根本不需要美化你
Y'know when I was telling all those guys about you, I didn't have to lie once.
真的吗  真的
Really? Yeah.
你是从Magma Ku Laude毕业的  是吧
You graduated magna cum laude, right?
不是
No.
噢  不要紧
Oh, it doesn't matter.
我有两张今晚球赛的门票  要不要跟我去看
Hey, y'know what, I've got two tickets to tonight's Rangers game, you wanna come with me?
看猛男穿短裤满场飞
Cute guys in little shorts?
当然
Sure.
但今晚是冰上曲棍球赛
Actually, it's a hockey team.
你只能看到  "愤怒无齿的加拿大人"（曲棍球队名）
so it's angry Canadians with no teeth.
好像挺好玩的  谢谢你
Well that sounds fun too. Thank you.
你有跟女人在一起过吗
Have you ever been with a woman?
什么
What?
钱德  你有毛病
Chandler, what is the matter with you?!
不管什么时候问这个问题  都会被人骂
So there is no good time to ask that question.
下一站是波放浦夕
The station is Poughkeepsie. Poughkeepsie!
罗斯
Ross?
醒醒
Wake up!
罗斯…
Ross? Ross! Ross!
我还要些旗鱼
I need more swordfish.
能帮我拿些旗鱼么  我不讲英文
Can you get me more swordfish? I don't speak English.
你刚讲的就是英文
You did a minute ago!
我只是不知道跟你说什么
well, I don't know what to tell you.
好吧
Fine.
好了  够了
Okay! Very funny!
谁来开下门
Somebody let me out please?!
快点  里面好冷
Come on, I'm cold!
现在又被泼了一身的酱汁
And covered in marinara sauce!
快点  放我出去
Come on! Let me out!
找到把手啦  是么
You found that handle, did you?
这一点也不好笑  谁说不好笑
It's not funny. Well, that's not true.
我是个好人  也是个好厨师
I'm a good person. And I'm a good chef.
我不该被弄得全身都是酱汁
and I don't deserve to have marinara sauce all over me!
如果你们想我辞职  只要
If you want me to quit this bad then you all have...
盖勒主厨
Hey. Chef Geller?
还记得那天你讲的那段话吗
Y'know that little speech you made the other day?
我有意见
I got a problem with it!
你不同意   没错
You do? You bet I do!
只是我当时没专心听  就是这样
I just, uh, wasn't listening then, that's all.
你想鸡蛋里挑骨头  就别怪我不客气了
Well if you want a problem, I'll give you a problem!
你想怎样  开除我吗
What are you going to do? Fire me?
那还用说  滚出我的厨房
You bet I'll fire you! Get out of my kitchen!
滚
Get out!
这才像话
All right.
还有谁有意见
Anybody else got a problem?
你呢  "偷笑先生"
How about you, chuckles?
你现在还觉得好笑吗
You think this is funny now?
不好笑
No.
我全身沾满酱汁跳舞  好不好笑
How about if I dance around all covered in sauce? Huh? You think it's funny now?
不  你跳得很好
No, it's really good.
沙拉送去给四号桌的客人
Good! Now, Take those salads to table four.
你去帮我拿鱼
And you, get the swordfish!
还有你…
And you!
去剪头发
Get a haircut!
终点站蒙特偌  蒙特偌到站了
Last stop, Montreal. The stop is Montreal!
什么
What?
我跟自己打赌  你的眼睛肯定很漂亮
I made a bet with myself that you had beautiful eyes.
看来  我赢了
Now that I see them, I win!
什么
What?
我要在这站下车  你想不想喝杯咖啡
We're at my stop. But would you like to have coffee?
我们真的在蒙特偌吗
Are we really in Montreal?
对  要不要
Yes, we are.
一起喝咖啡
So coffee?
好主意
Coffee sounds great.
等等
Wait, so,
你住在蒙特偌
So you live in Montreal?
不  我住新斯科细亚  坐渡轮两小时就到了
Oh, no. But it's a two hour ferry ride to Nova Scotia.
在我跟主厨顶嘴之前
Well I guess I should've thought about my wife and kids...
真该想想家中妻小
...before I talked back to Chef Geller.
谢了
Thanks.
看来今年我们全家只能过个艰苦的圣诞节了
Yep! Looks like it's gonna be a leeeeean Christmas at the Dragon house this year.
够了
Enough!
穷啊  穷啊  穷啊
Lean, lean, lean!
来到储藏室  坐在圣诞老人的腿上
Went to the store Sat on Santa's lap
要他送堆礼物给我朋友
Asked him to bring my friends All kinds of crap
他说你只需要帮他们写首歌
Said all you need is To write them a song
这首歌你们没听过  别想跟着我唱
Now you haven't heard it yet So don't try to sing along
不要跟我唱
No, don't sing along
摩妮卡…
Monica, Monica
光明节快乐
Have a happy Hanukkah
我看到圣诞老公公
Saw Santa Claus
他要我跟罗斯打招呼
He said hello to Ross
请告诉乔伊
And please tell Joey
圣诞节将瑞雪纷飞
Christmas will be snowy
还有瑞秋和钱德  有  鼻膈炎
And Rachel and Chandler, have err-umm-glander!!
祝各位佳节快乐
Happy holidays, everybody!